Berryman Family
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
- Clifford and Kate Berryman Papers, 1829-1963, undated, Series 1:; (boxes 1-7, sols 11-12, OVs 14-15, 7.9 linear ft.)
  - Correspondence, 1829-1953, undated, 1.3:
    Howard E. P. (N.Y. Press): 03 Apr 1927, 26 Mar 1927, 15 Apr 1927, 23 Jan 1928
    Hubbard, Kin (cartoonist, Indianapolis News): 10 Feb 1913, 15 Feb 1913, 31 Jul 1914
    Hughes, Charles Evans (Secretary of State): 15 Apr 1921 (printed invitation)
    Hughes, R. E. (La. Purchase Exposition): 15 Mar 1904
    Humphrey, William E. (Federal Trade Commission): undated (illustrated letter), 20 Jan 1933
    Hutchison, George W. (National Geographic Society): 09 Dec 1935, 01 Apr 1937
    Ickes, Harold L. (Secretary of the Interior): 09 Mar 1935, 08 Nov 1935, 20 May 1936, 29 Nov 1938, 11 Dec 1939, 05 Jun 1941, 09 Jun 1941, 13 Jun 1941, 17 Jun 1941 (letter from Mrs. Ickes), 13 Feb 1942, 27 Apr 1942, 04 May 1942, 15 Jun 1943, 21 Jun 1943, 05 May 1944, 15 Dec 1949
    Ireland, William A. (Columbus Dispatch): 21 Mar 1913, 16 Mar 1917 (letter of introduction for Will Rogers), 01 Mar 1926
    Jackson, Robert H. (Attorney General): 08 Feb 1938, 05 Dec 1938, 05 Dec 1940
    James, Ollie M. (Congressman?, Kentucky): 20 Jan 1910
    Johnson, Albert (Congressman, Washington): 24 Nov 1913, 20 Feb 1915, 02 Jun 1926, 18 Apr 1929, 31 Mar 1932
    Johnson, Andrew: 19 Aug 1861 (letter to A. M. Coffin not in Johnson's hand)
    Johnson, Herbert (art editor, Saturday Evening Post): 09 Sep 1913, 16 Sep 1913, 23 Feb 1928, 11 May 1934
    Johnson, Herschel V. (US Representative to UN): 12 Sep 1937, 22 Oct 1947
    Johnson, Hiram W. (Senator, California): 11 Feb 1920, 01 Nov 1940
    Johnson, Nelson T. (Asst. Sec. of State): 21 Dec 1928
    Johnson, Philander Chase: 03 Jan 1908
    Johnston, John A. (General): 05 Apr 1919
    Jones, E. Lester (US Coast & Geodetic Survey): 10 Mar 1920
    Jones, Jesse H. (Secretary of Commerce): 24 Dec 1941, 29 May 1942, 13 Oct 1943, 04 Dec 1943, 02 May 1944
    Jones, Marvin (Congressman, Texas): 24 Feb 1936
    Jones, Wesley L. (Senator): 07 May 1920, 18 Feb 1925
    Kahn, Julius (Congressman, California): 17 Mar 1920, 13 Apr 1920
    Kauffmann, Rudolph Max (Washington Star): 05 Oct 1920, 16 Apr 1947, 12 May 1947
    Kearns, (Senator): undated
    Keefe, Frank B. (Congressman, Wisconsin): 29 Jul 1947
    Kelly, Clyde (Congressman, Pennsylvania): 14 Feb 1928
    Kelly, Hugh A. (Governor, New Jersey): 14 May 1938
    Kelly, J. (editor, Chicago Tribune): 02 Jun 1906
    Kendrick, John B. (Governor, Wyoming): 30 Sep 1916 (letter about him)
    Kennedy, Joseph P. (Chairman, US Maritime Commission): 24 Sep 1937
    Kenyon, William S. (Senator, Iowa): 29 Mar 1916, 27 Sep 1916
    Keyes, Frances Parkinson: 18 Jul 1921
    Keyes, Henry W. (Senator, New Hampshire): 25 Feb 1925
    King, Ernest J. (Admiral): 24 Nov 1942, 06 Nov 1944
    Kirchhope, Alt? (Buffalo Evening News): 26 Mar 1927
    Kitchin, Claude (Congressman): 06 Mar 1916, 31 Mar 1916
    Knutson, Harold, (Congressman, Minnesota): 04 Mar 1948
    LaFollette, Robert M., Jr. (Senator, Wisconsin): 03 Jul 1929, 09 Mar 1931 (letter about him)
    La Gorce, John Oliver (National Geographic Society): undated, 27 Feb 1912, 18 Jun 1943, 02 May 1944, 31 May 1949
    Land, E. S. (Chairman, US Maritime Commission): 10 Mar 1941
    Land, George A. (Congressman): 03 Mar 1904
    Landis, C. B. (Congressman, Indiana): undated, 11 Nov 1904
    Landon, Alf M. (Governor, Kansas): 30 Oct 1935, 14 Jan 1936, 24 Mar 1936, 08 Aug 1936, 26 Dec 1936, 02 Feb 1937, 27 Feb 1937, 13 Oct 1943, 16 May 1944, 20 Nov 1944, 01 Apr 1948
    Lane, Franklin K. (Secretary of the Interior): undated, 15 Mar 1913, 18 Mar 1913, 31 Dec 1913, 06 Mar 1916, 13 Mar 1916, 08 Jan 1917, 21 Dec 1918, 11 Feb 1920, 13 Feb 1918, 12 Mar 1918, 19 Mar 1918, 22 Mar 1920
    Lansburgh, Henry: 30 Dec 1915
    Lansburgh, Mark (Lansburgh & Bro.): 16 Apr 1931, 05 Nov 1932
    Lansing, Robert (Secretary of State): 28 Mar 1916, 25 Jan 1917, 08 Feb 1918, 24 Feb 1920, 29 Apr 1924
    Lauder, Harry: undated
    Lewis, B. J. (Knickerbocker News): 13 Mar 1941
    Lewis, Fulton (WOL Radio): 17 Aug 1938
    Lewis, James Hamilton, (Senator, Illinois): 30 Mar 1916, 15 Jan 1919, 26 Feb 1919, 07 Feb 1930, 16 Feb 1933, 13 May 1937
    Lewis, John L.: 17 Apr 1937
    Lewis, William Mather (Pres., George Washington U. and Pres., Lafayette College): 19 Sep 1924, 11 Oct 1929, 09 Dec 1931 (letter about him), 24 Mar 1942, 31 Mar 1942, 07 May 1944
    Lindsay, R. C. (British Embassy): 26 May 1939
    Lineberger, Walter F. (Congressman, Ca.): 01 Jun 1926
    Lobeck, C. O. (Congressman, Nebraska): 11 Mar 1916, 01 Apr 1916
    Locke, M. E. (Brigadier General): 24 May 1941
    Lodge, Henry Cabot (Senator, Massachusetts): 18 Feb 1907, 22 Jul 1910, 22 Jul 1942
    Lohr, Lenox (NBC): 29 June 1938, 29 Jul 1938
    Long, B. (Asst. Secretary of State): 11 May 1942
    Loring, Paule: undated, 13 Oct 1936 (illustrated letter)
    Lowden, Frank O. (Governor, Illinois): 26 Jan 1920, 14 Feb 1920
    Ludlow, Louis (Pioneer Book Co.): 14 Feb 1925, 25 Dec 1926, 20 Nov 1941, 20 Dec 1941
    Luther, Dr. Hans (German Ambassador): undated
    MacVeagh, Franklin (Sec. of the Treasury): 18 May 1911
    Mahony, Felix: undated (illustrated letter)
    Maloney, Francis (Senator, Connecticut); 11 Sep 1941, 22 Sep 1941, 06 Jan 1943, 02 May 1944
    Mann, James R. (Congressman, Illinois): Oct 28, 1913, 07 Dec 1918, 01 Mar 1921
    Marshall, George Catlett (General): 13 Jun 1940, 01 Apr 1944 (letter from his wife)
    Martin, Joseph W., Jr. (Congressman, Massachusetts): 05 Jan 1942 (letter about him), 09 Mar 1942, 17 Apr 1943, 05 May 1944
    Martin, Thomas S. (Senator): 07 Feb 1912
    Marvin, Cloyd H. (Pres., George Washington U.): 06 Apr 1944
    Maxwell, G. T. (cartoonist?): 14 Jul 1914
    McAdams, Clark (President, St. Louis Artists' Guild): 06 Jan 1914, 20 Jan 1914
    McAdoo, William G. (Secretary of the Treasury): 06 Jun 1914, 11 Jan 1914, 15 Feb 1917, 02 Mar 1917 (letter about him), 03 Sep 1918, 21 Nov 1922, 09 Aug 1925
    McCarran, Patrick (Senator, Nevada): 23 May 1941
    McClellan, George S.: 14 Feb 1938
    McClure, Samuel G. (editor, Ohio State Journal): 23 Jul 1903
    McCormack, John W. (Congressman, Massachusetts): 06 Aug 1944
    McCumber (Senator, North Dakota): 29 Oct 1919
    McCutcheon, John T. (Chicago Tribune): 02 Dec 1907, 04 Apr 1913, 30 Dec 1913
    McDonald, C. P. (Chicago Tribune): 19 Aug 1909
    McDonald, Eugene F. (President, Zenith Radio Corp.): 20 Jan 1940 (letter to R. D. Heinl re FDR), 13 Nov 1939
    McDuffie, John (Congressman, Alabama): 16 Apr 1934
    McKellar, Kenneth (Senator, Tennessee): 19 Mar 1942, 31 Mar 1944
    McKelway, Ben M. (ed., Washington Star): 20 Oct 1947
    McKenna, Joseph (Supreme Court Justice): 27 Feb 1923
    McKinley, William B. (Senator, Illinois): undated, 06 Feb 1913, 03 Mar 1913, 04 Aug 1920
    McLean, Edward B. (Inaugural Committee): 23 Dec 1920
    McNair, Lesley James (General): 19 Jun 1944, 19 Jun 1944 (letter from his wife)
    McReynolds, James C. (Supreme Court Justice): 11 Feb 1920, 09 Feb 1937 (letter from Mrs.McReynolds)
    Mellon, Andrew (Secretary of the Treasury): 13 Apr 1925 (letter about him)
    Meredith, Edwin T. (Sec. of Agriculture): 13 Feb 1920
    Merrick, Frank L. (Louisiana Purchase Exposition): 18 Aug 1903, 20 Aug 1927
    Meyer, George von L. (Sec. of the Navy): 23 Jan 1911
    Meyers, Eugene (Washington Post): 14 Jun 1938, 27 Feb 1941 (printed invitation), 11 May 1944, 29 Jul 1949
    Michelson, Charles (Democratic National Committee): 16 Oct 1935 (2), 21 Sep 1936, 29 Sep 1936
    Millard, Charles D. (Congressman, N. Y.): 21 Feb 1935
    Miller, James M. (Congressman): 17 Mar 1909 (letter from Mrs. Miller)
    Mills, Ogden L. (Undersecretary of the Treasury): 22 Apr 1931
    Minnigerode, C. Powell (Dir., Corcoran Gallery of Art): 27 Dec 1918 (2), 18 Jun 1943 (illustrated letter)
    Minor, Benjamin S. (Inaugural Committee): 15 Jan 1913
    Mitchell, Mrs. William Dewitt: 02 Mar 1931
    Mondell, Frank W. (Congressman, Wyoming): 08 Apr 1920
    Montgomery, James Shera (Chaplain, House of Representatives): 06 Aug 1918, 19 Jul 1919, 14 Jul 1945
    Moore, J. Hampton (Congressman, Pa. and Mayor of Philadelphia): 17 Mar 1905, 28 May 1908, 29 Dec 1909, 29 Mar 1910, 01 Apr 1910, 04 Apr 1910, 07 Apr 1910, 27 Apr 1911, 27 Jan 1914, 23 Feb 1914, 08 Feb 1918, 14 Feb 1923, 09 Mar 1923, 23 Oct 1923, 05 Mar 1925, 31 Mar 1925, 15 Apr 1925 (2), 28 Jul 1925, 17 Oct 1925
    Morgenthau, Henry, Jr. (Secretary of the Treasury): 05 Mar 1936, 10 Dec 1936, 23 Apr 1937, 12 Dec 1940, 18 Mar 1941, 22 Apr 1941, 09 May 1941, 03 Jul 1941
    Moses, George H. (Senator, N. H.): 19 Jan 1922, 25 Jul 1923, 10 Feb 1927, 15 Dec 1927, 17 Dec 1927, 16 Jan 1929, 15 Aug 1929 (letter about him)
    Murdock, Victor (Congressman, Kansas): undated (2), 01 Mar 1915, 18 Oct 1940
    Murphy, Francis P. (Governor, N. H.): 27 Jan 1938 (2)
    Murphy, J. E. (Oregon Journal): 14 Sep 1913
    Murphy, William C. (Philadelphia Inquirer): 12 May 1941
    Neely, Matthew M. (Governor, W. V.): 16 Jan 1941
    New, Harry S. (Postmaster General): 30 Jul 1924, 10 Jan 1927
    Newcome, W. A. (Ambassador to Italy): 13 Feb 1913
    Nimitz, Chester W. (Admiral): 28 Nov 1942 (letter from his daughter Catherine), 15 Mar 1944
    North, James (cartoonist?): 14 May 1921, 16 May 1921
    Norton, Mary T. (Congresswoman, New Jersey): 09 Aug 1937, 13 Aug 1937, 06 Dec 1937, 30 Jun 1942
    Noyes, Newbold: 13 Jan 1927 (letter from Mrs. Clarence Williams)
    Noyes, Theodore W.: undated (3), 01 Jul 1918, 13 Mar 1920, 08 Jul 1929, 23 Apr 1930, 27 Feb 1934
    O'Connor, John H. (Congressman, New York): 05 Jan 1937
    Oliver, W. B. (Congressman, Alabama): 16 Feb 1924
    Olney, Richard (Congressman, Mass.): 01 Apr 1920
    O'Neal, Sam (Pres., National Press Club): 22 Jun 1944
    Osborn, F. H. (Brigadier General): 16 Jan 1942
    Ourand, Chas. H. (Isthmian Canal Commission): 20 Mar 1913
    Owen, Ruth Bryan (Congresswoman, Florida): 09 Nov 1932
    Palmer, A. Mitchell (Attorney General): 12 Feb 1920, 01 Apr 1920
    Parsons, R. C. (editor, Cleveland Leader): 04 Mar 1898
    Patrick, Geo. H.: 01 Jun 1906 (re McClellan statue), 07 Jun 1906
    Peaslee, Horace W. (architect): 25 Mar 1941
    Penrose, Boies (Senator, Pennsylvania): 15 Jun 1906
    Pepper, Claude (Senator, Florida): 13 Mar 1942, 03 Nov 1943, 17 Apr 1945
    Perkins, Francis (Secretary of Labor): 24 Jul 1942
    Pershing, John J. (General): 28 May 1945 (autographed card)
    Phelan, James D. (Senator, California): 28 Jun 1918, 05 Jun 1920
    Phipps, Lawrence C. (Senator, Colorado): 07 May 1920, 03 Mar 1923
    Pike, Albert (Department of the Interior): undated
    Poindexter, Miles (Senator, Washington): 13 Feb 1920
    Polk, Frank L. (Undersecretary of State): 25 Mar 1920
    Pomerene, Atlee (Senator, Ohio): 01 Jun 1911 (letter from Mrs. Pomerene), 20 Feb 1920 (letter from Mrs. Pomerene), 01 Mar 1920 (letter from Mrs. Pomerene), 08 May 1920
    Porter, Laura (League of Women Voters): 28 Dec 1930
    Pou, Edw. W. (Congressman, North Carolina): 30 Sep 1904, 07 Oct 1904, 10 Oct 1904, 17 Oct 1904
    Powers, Samuel Leland (Congressman, Massachusetts): 17 Feb 1905, 30 Dec 1925
    Proctor, Redfield (Senator): 21 Jun 1906
    Radcliffe, George L. (Senator, Maryland): 15 Sep 1938
    Rainey, Henry T. (Congressman, Illinois): 07 Mar 1916
    Ralston, Samuel M. (Senator, Indiana): 30 May 1924
    Ramspeck, Robert (Congressman, Georgia): 28 Nov 1941
    Rankin, J. E. (Congressman, Mississippi): 14 Feb 1942
    Rathbun, Richard (Asst. Secretary of Smithsonian): 11 Apr 1912, 07 Dec 1915
    Rayburn, Sam: 24 Mar 1944
    Reams, Frank (White House staff): 10 Jan 1929
    Redfield, William C. (Secretary of Commerce): 31 Aug 1912, 07 Nov 1913, 07 Apr 1915, 07 Mar 1916
    Reed, Daniel (Congressman, New York): Apr 28, 1920
    Reed, Stanley F. (Supreme Court Justice): 13 Mar 1948
    Reed, Stuart F. (Congressman, W. V.): 27 Mar 1922
    Reid, Albert T. (American Artists Professional League): 02 May 1944
    Rhodes, John D. (Senator): undated, 01 Nov 1943
    Ritchie, Albert C. (Governor, Maryland): 15 Nov 1923 (2), 14 May 1924, 23 Dec 1925, 28 Dec 1926, 09 Jan 1927, 14 Jan 1927, 10 Feb 1927, 20 Jan 1931, 07 Aug 1931, 30 Jan 1936
    Robertson, David A. (President, Goucher College): 15 Dec 1939 (letter from Anne Robertson), 19 Apr 1932, 18 Dec 1942, 14 Aug 1943
    Robinson, Boardman (New York Tribune): 21 Mar 1913, 02 Jun 1913
    Robinson, Joe T. (Senator, Arkansas): 10 Mar 1916, 29 Nov 1921, 25 Apr 1936
    Rodman, Hugh (Admiral): 10 Nov 1937
    Rogers, Edith Nourse (Congresswoman, Massachusetts): 15 Feb 1937, 16 Feb 1937
    Rogers, W. A.: 19 Mar 1925, 10 Apr 1925
    Rogers, Will: 16 Mar 1917 (letter of introduction from Bill Ireland), 19 Aug 1927 (invitation to Press Club dinner in his honor)
    Roosevelt, Franklin D.: 26 Apr 1935 (letter about him), 20 Jan 1940 (letter about him), 08 Jul 1940 (photograph of letter)
    Roosevelt, Theodore: 29 Dec 1902, 09 Jan 1912
    Root, Elihu (Secretary of State): 14 Dec 1905
    Roper, Daniel C. (Secretary of Commerce): undated, 18 Aug 1913, 16 Sep 1932, 15 Aug 1933, 07 Sep 1933, 11 Nov 1933, 14 Aug 1934, 10 Dec 1934, 18 May 1936, 16 Nov 1937, 05 Aug 1938
    Ross, Nellie Tayloe (Democratic National Committee): 10 Dec 1932
    Roteler, J. Allen: 23 Feb 1936 (letter re Andrew Mellon and the Corcoran Gallery)
    Russell, K. L. (cartoonist?): 11 Jun 1906 (illustrated letter)
    Russell, Richard (Senator and Governor of Florida): 29 Mar 1944, 22 Mar 1949
    Sabath, A. J. (Congressman, Illinois): 24 Feb 1941, 19 Jan 1945
    Sackett, Frederic M. (Senator, Kentucky): 24 Oct 1925
    Saltonstall, Leverett (Senator, Mass.): 12 Apr 1948
    Sanders, Everett (Congressman, Indiana): 19 Feb 1925, 02 Jul 1932
    Saulsbury, Willard (Senator, Delaware): 21 Oct 1918 (letter to Col. E. A. Halsey)
    Scott, Hugh D., Jr. (Congressman, Pa.): 10 Oct 1949
    Seger, George N. (Congressman, N. J.): 13 Jan 1925
    Seton, Grace Thompson (National League of American Pen Women): 12 Mar 1927, 12 Apr 1927, 11 May 1927
    Shaw, Albert P.: 08 Nov 1901, 08 Nov 1926, 09 Nov 1926, 09 Jan 1933 (letter from C. Berryman)
    Shaw, Leslie M.: 11 Oct 1905 (printed invitation)
    Sheppard, Morris (Senator, Texas): 08 May 1920, 10 Oct 1924, 15 Nov 1924, 05 Sep 1933, 31 Dec 1937, 13 Oct 1938, 08 Nov 1938, 10 Aug 1940, 19 Sep 1940
    Sherman, Lawrence Y. (Senator, Illinois): 08 Feb 1918
    Shih, Hu (Chinese Embassy): 07 Dec 1939, 27 Nov 1941
    Shoemaker, Vaughn (cartoonist, Chicago Daily News): 29 Mar 1945
    Shoppell, R. W. (National Tribune): 02 Dec 1904
    Slemp, C. B. (Congressman, Virginia): 31 Aug 1914, 10 Mar 1916
    Smith, Alfred (Governor, New York): 07 May 1924
    Smith, John Walter (Senator, Maryland): 11 Mar 1916
    Smoot, Reed (Senator): 29 Jun 1906, 07 May 1920
    Smoot, William (Governor, Pennsylvania): 13 Jan 1922
    Snell, Bertrand H. (Congressman): 31 May 1929
    Snow, William J. (Major General): 06 Jan 1919, 14 Jan 1921
    Snyder, John W. (Sec. of the Treasury): 23 Jun 1947
    Somerville, Harry P. (The Willard): 01 Apr 1936, 09 Jul 1936, 10 Apr 1942
    Spooner, John C. (Senator, Wisconsin): 07 Mar 1907
    Stand, Bert (Democratic County Committee): 02 Jun 1936
    Stanley, Augustus O. (Senator, Kentucky): 20 Feb 1907, 25 Mar 1920, 13 Aug 1921, 19 Aug 1921, 09 Nov 1935
    Stettinius, Edward R. (Secretary of State): 15 Sep 1944, 26 Oct 1944, 13 Mar 1945, 29 Mar 1945
    Stimson, Henry L. (Sec. of State and Sec. of War): 06 Feb 1912, 21 Dec 1932, 29 Apr 1943
    Stone, Harlan F. (Supreme Court Justice); 02 May 1944
    Strick (National Press Club): undated
    Sulzer, William (candidate for Governor): 21 Jul 1914 (3), 21 Jul 1914 (letter from Mrs. Sulzer)
    Suter, John Wallace (Dean, Washington Cathedral): 13 Feb 1945, 12 Mar 1945
    Sutherland, Howard (Senator): 10 Feb 1920, 07 May 1920
    Swanson, Claude A. (Senator, Virginia): 18 Aug 1910, 15 Oct 1919
    Swing, Phil D. (Congressman, California): 20 Dec 1932
    Sylvester, Arthur (Newark Evening News): 23 Jun 1947
    Sylvester, Richard (Inaugural Committee): 31 Dec 1904
    Taft, William Howard: 10 May 1907, 30 Jun 1908, 18 Mar 1925 (letter about him)
    Taliaferro, Sidney F. (DC Commissioner): 13 Apr 1927
    Tharin, Charles E. (White House staff): 14 Jun 1905
    Thomas, Elmer (Senator, Oklahoma): 02 Jul 1936
    Thompson, Charles Willis (New York Times): 13 Mar 1905
    Thornton, J. R. (Senator): 16 Dec 1910, 10 Dec 1912, 12 Dec 1912, 22 Nov 1913, 18 Mar 1914, 21 Mar 1914, 11 Feb 1915, 15 Mar 1915, 01 Jul 1916
    Tilson, John Q. (Congressman, Conn.): 18 Apr 1929
    Tobey, Charles W. (Senator, N. H.): 12 Jan 1948
    Tony, F. A. (Strand magazine): 06 Nov 1914
    Towner, H. M. (Governor, Puerto Rico): 14 Jul 1924, 15 Apr 1925
    Treadway, Allen T. (Congressman, Mass.): 25 May 1935
    Trimble, South (Congressman): 24 Nov 1915, 11 Mar 1938
    Trinkle, E. Lee (Governor, Virginia): 04 Feb 1925, 02 Mar 1925, 22 Jun 1925, 08 Jan 1926
    Truesdell, George: 08 Jun 1906 (re McClellan statue)
    Truman, Bess: 31 May 1949
    Truman, Harry S: 07 Jun 1945 (copy of letter to Col. Johnson), 29 Mar 1946
    Tydings, Millard E. (Senator, Maryland): 10 May 1935, 14 May 1935, 10 Jun 1938, 17 Jun 1938, 09 Sep 1938, 20 Sep 1938, 07 Mar 1944, 01 May 1944, 09 May 1944
    Underwood, Oscar W. (Congressman, Alabama): 26 Feb 1912, 10 Mar 1916, 06 Jan 1917, 11 Feb 1920
    Vincent, B. M. (Congressman, Kentucky): 07 Sep 1940 (letter about him)
    Vinson, Carl (Congressman, Georgia): 09 Jun 1920
    Wadsworth, James W. (Congressman, N. Y.): 13 Feb 1941
    Walker, Frank C. (Postmaster General): 26 Nov 1941, 05 Nov 1943, 06 Jul 1943
    Wallace, Henry A. (Secretary of Agriculture): undated (2), one illustrated), 01 Feb 1937, 06 Dec 1937
    Ward, H. S. (Congressman, North Carolina): undated
    Warner, V. (Congressman): 14 Jan 1905
    Warren, Francis E. (Senator): 10 May 1920, 15 Oct 1924, 18 Oct 1924 (letter about him), 24 Nov 1924, 17 Feb 1925
    Warren, Lindsay C. (Congressman, North Carolina): 11 Mar 1935, 13 Mar 1935
    Watterson, Henry (Courier-Journal): 22 Apr 1912 (2)
    Webster, Harold Tucker: 17 May 1918, 01 Jul 1918, 17 Jul 1918, 29 Aug 1918 (2), 09 Oct 1918, 06 Nov 1918
    Westerman (Ohio State Journal): undated
    Wetmore, A. (Smithsonian Institution): 26 Jul 1944
    Wheeler, Burton K. (Senator, Montana): undated (letter from Mrs. Wheeler), 27 Jan 1937, 05 Aug 1941
    White, Edward D. (Supreme Court Justice): 06 Feb 1917
    Wickard, Claude R. (Secretary of Agriculture): 30 Jan 1942, 11 Feb 1942, 16 Apr 1942
    Wickersham, George W.: 23 Dec 1930, 17 Dec 1934
    Wile, Frederic William: 12 May 1924 (letter of introduction for William Schofield), 15 Nov 1928
    Williams, John Sharp (Senator): 14 May 1914
    Willis, Frank B. (Senator, Ohio): 13 Feb 1928
    Willkie, Wendell L.: 02 May 1944
    Wilson, Charles R. (candidate for Mayor, Huntington West Virginia): 21 Mar 1928, 14 May 1932
    Wilson, Edith Bolling: 26 Mar 1916, 10 Feb 1917
    Wilson, James (Secretary of Agriculture): 30 Jan 1909
    Wilson, Lyle C. (United Press Assocs.): 29 Mar 1945
    Wilson, Woodrow: 04 Dec 1916
    Winslow, Samuel E. (Congressman, Massachusetts): 13 Feb 1920, 20 Feb 1925
    Wood, Edwin O. (Democratic National Committee): 09 Dec 1911 (2), 24 Jul 1914, 10 Sep 1914
    Wood, Will R. (Congressman, Indiana): 20 Jul 1916, 03 Mar 1925
    Woodin, William H. (Sec. of the Treasury): 07 Jun 1933
    Woodward, Donald (Woodward & Lothrop department store): 17 Jan 1921
    Work, Hubert (Secretary of the Interior): 31 Dec 1926, 12 Jan 1927, 23 Jun 1928
    Works?, John D. (Senator): 29 Mar 1916
    Young, George M. (Congressman, N. D.): 07 Oct 1925
    Zears, Guy (Congressman): 28 Dec 1940
    Zihlman, Frederick N. (Congressman, Md.): 10 Feb 1927
    Zimmerman, Eugene “ZIM” (cartoonist): 02 Jul 1929 (letter about him from Freeman H. Hubbard), 05 Jul 1929 (letter about ZIM from C.Berryman)
    - Scrapbook of greeting cards illustrated by Clifford and Jim Berryman, 1901-1934 (Box 1, Reel 4768)
    - General correspondence, 1829-1916, undated, (69 folders) (Box 2, Reel 4769)
    - General correspondence, 1917-April, 1925, (44 folders) (Box 3, Reel 4769)
    - General correspondence, May, 1925-1928, (18 folders) (Box 3, Reel 4770)
    - General correspondence, 1929-1938, (60 folders) (Box 4, Reel 4770)
    - General correspondence, 1939-April, 1942, (25 folders) (Box 5, Reel 4770)
    - General correspondence, April, 1942-April, 1953, (41 folders) (Box 5, Reel 4771)
  - Business Records, 1874-1937, 1.4:
    This series consists of receipts and legal records which include a 1903 copyright document for C. Berryman's cartoons of the 58th House, and a 1937 codicil to Kate Berryman's will.
    - Financial records, receipts, 1874-1936 (Box 6, Reel 4771)
    - Legal records, 1903, 1937 (Box 6, Reel 4771)
  - Notes, 1940-1963, undated, 1.5:
    The Cultus Club guest book found here includes cartoons by Jim Berryman, Gib Crockett, and the Minnigerodes, and notes of William E. Knight's 80th birthday.
    - Guest book for the Cultus Club hosted by Kate Berryman, 1940-1963 (Box 6, Reel 4771)
    - List of works by Clifford Berryman, circa 1943-1945 (Box 6, Reel 4771)
    - Miscellaneous notes, undated (Box 6, Reel 4771)
  - Writings, 1944-1946, undated, 1.6:
    This series includes lecture notes, manuscripts for speeches, poems, typescripts of writings by others, and miscellaneous writings.
    - Lecture notes, undated (Box 6, Reel 4771)
    - Manuscripts for speeches, undated (Box 6, Reel 4771)
    - Poems, undated (Box 6, Reel 4771)
    - Typescripts of writings by others, 1944-1946 (Box 6, Reel 4771)
    - Miscellaneous writings, 1946, undated (Box 6, Reel 4771)
  - Artwork, circa 1882-1945, undated, 1.7:
    Artwork consists of two sketchbooks, including one from Clifford's childhood, cartoon portraits, political cartoons, cartoons of Gridiron Club skits, and miscellaneous drawings. Also found is artwork by others including Frank Barnard, Casterlind, Cesar, Davenport, Buddy Flake, Frank Godwin, and A. Parker, Will Robinson. See also box 11 (sol), OV 14, and OV 15 for oversized artwork including political cartoons.
    - Sketchbook, circa 1882-1885 (Box 6, Reel 4771)
    - Sketchbook, 1889 (Box 6, Reel 4771)
    - Cartoon portraits (see also sol 11, OV 14, OV 15), 1912-1945, undated, (7 folders) (Box 6, Reel 4771)
    - Drawings on Acetate, circa 1912-1918 (Box 6, Reel 4771)
    - Miscellaneous cartoons, undated (Box 6, Reel 4771)
    - Cartoons (50) of Gridiron Club skits, undated, (5 folders) (Box 6, Reel 4771)
    - Miscellaneous drawings (38), 1913-1942, undated, (2 folders) (Box 6, Reel 4771)
    - Artwork by others, 1903, undated (Box 6, Reel 4771)
  - Scrapbooks, 1902-circa 1945, 1.8:
    This series consists of a scrapbook volume of clippings, some loose pages of clippings and photographs, and a scrapbook of memorabilia collected by Kate Berryman regarding her husband. The latter, titled "Treasures and Heart Throbs," includes letters from Bernard Baruch, William Jennings Bryan, Harry Flood Byrd, Jay Darling, John Nance Garner, Herbert Hoover, Henry Cabot Lodge, Harry Truman, and Woodrow Wilson. Also included are clippings, cartoons, printed material, and photographs of Clifford family members, William Jennings Bryan, John Nance Garner, Brenda Putnam, and William Howard Taft.
    - Scrapbook of clippings, 1902-1905 (Box 6, Reel 4771)
    - Scrapbook (fragment), clippings and photographs, circa 1938 (Box 6, Reel 4771)
    - Scrapbook, "Treasures and Heart Throbs," 1905-1945, (3 folders) (Box 16 (pam), Reel D111)
  - Printed Material, 1856-1972, undated, 1.9: